export const data = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is the 7ESL App?",
    answer:
      "The 7ESL App is a sophisticated English learning tool designed to help you speak English fluently. It uses advanced AI technology to simulate real-life conversations, provide lessons from AI tutors, and offer immediate feedback through AI examiners to help you master English effectively.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: ". How does the Chunking Method work?",
    answer:
      "The Chunking Method focuses on learning phrases instead of individual words. This method allows you to construct sentences more naturally, making it easier to speak English fluently. You learn sets of words that frequently go together, which helps in understanding and producing language quickly.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Is the 7ESL App suitable for beginners?",
    answer:
      "Yes, the 7ESL App caters to all levels of English learners, from beginners to advanced. It offers customized learning paths that include basic phrases for beginners and more complex language structures for advanced learners.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Can I improve my English pronunciation with the 7ESL App?",
    answer:
      "Absolutely! The app includes a detailed pronunciation report that analyses your speech, highlights the sounds you need to improve, and offers practice exercises to enhance your pronunciation.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "How are the AI Examiners helpful?",
    answer:
      "AI Examiners in the 7ESL App conduct simulated tests covering various topics. You receive immediate results along with detailed feedback on your pronunciation, fluency, vocabulary, and grammar. This helps identify areas of improvement and track your progress.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What are Daily Missions?",
    answer:
      "Daily Missions are personalized tasks designed to improve specific areas of your English proficiency. Completing these missions helps you practice consistently and earn rewards, making learning both fun and effective.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "How does the 7ESL App differ from other English learning apps?",
    answer:
      "Unlike many other apps, the 7ESL App uses AI-driven interactions and provides a comprehensive, four-step learning process that covers learning, practicing, testing, and improving your English. It's designed to feel like you're engaging in a game, making learning enjoyable and interactive.",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      "How does the free version differ from Pro and Premium subscriptions?",
    answer:
      "The free version serves as a basic introduction to the 7ESL App, allowing limited access to AI tutors, examiners, characters and speaking practice features. Pro and Premium tiers offer more in-depth features and unrestricted access to educational resources, making them suitable for users who are serious about improving their English fluently and effectively.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "How do I upgrade from a Free subscription to Pro or Premium?",
    answer:
      "You can easily upgrade through the appâ€™s subscription section. Choose the desired plan (Pro or Premium), select the subscription duration (6 months or 1 year), and complete the payment process. Your account will be upgraded instantly.",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "What kind of support is available for Pro or Premium subscribers?",
    answer:
      "Pro and Premium subscribers have access to priority customer support, including quicker responses and more personalized assistance to ensure the best possible learning experience.",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "How is my initial English level assessed in the 7ESL App?",
    answer:
      "Upon starting with the 7ESL app, new users are required to take 5 speaking tests with our AI examiners. These initial tests determine your English proficiency level, which is categorized according to the Common European Framework of Reference for Languages (CEFR) from levels A1 (beginner) to C2 (mastery).",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "What happens after my English level is assessed?",
    answer:
      "Based on your assessed level, you will receive personalized learning paths tailored to your proficiency. From A1 to C2, each level has specific tasks that you must complete to progress to the next level. These tasks can include completing a certain number of lessons from AI tutors, mastering learning chunks, or engaging in real-life speaking practices with AI characters.",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "Is my data safe with the 7ESL App?",
    answer:
      "Yes, data security and privacy are priorities for us. We use encrypted systems to protect your personal information and ensure that your data is handled with stringent security measures. For any more questions or support, feel free to contact our customer service through the app or visit our website.",
  },
];
